Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #11, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #11 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #12, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #12 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #13, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #13 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #14, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #14 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #15, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #15 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #16, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #16 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #17, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- 05-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #17 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- 05-01-4-2 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- 05-01-4-2 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 50)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 51)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 52)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 53)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 54)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 55)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 56)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 57)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 58)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 59)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 60)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 61)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 62)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 63)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 64)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 65)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #15, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 66)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #15 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 67)
- 05-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #16, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 68)
- 05-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #16 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 69)
- 05-01-2-2 - "B" Manager Interview #17, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 70)
- 05-01-2-2 - "B" Manager Interview #17 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 71)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 72)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 73)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #19, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 74)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #19 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 75)
- 05-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #20, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 76)
- 05-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #20 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 77)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #21, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 78)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #21 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 79)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #22, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 80)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #22 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 81)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #23, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 82)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #23 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 83)
- 05-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #24, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 84)
- 05-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #24 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 85)
- 05-01-6-1 - "B" Manager Interview #25, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 86)
- 05-01-6-1 - "B" Manager Interview #25 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 87)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #26, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 88)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #26 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 89)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #30, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #30 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #31, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #31 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- 05-01-3-1 - "B" Manager Interview #32, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- 05-01-3-1 - "B" Manager Interview #32 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #27, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #27 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #28, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #28 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #29, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- 05-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #29 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- 05-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program #5, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- 05-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program #5 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- 05-01-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- 05-01-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- 05-01-1-1 - Membership Information Summary #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- 05-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Western Electric Individual Case Data - Philadelphia, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- 03-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- 04-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 49)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 50)
- 04-02-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- 04-02-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 52)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 53)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 54)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 55)
- 04-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 56)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 57)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 58)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 59)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 60)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 61)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 62)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 63)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 64)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 65)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 66)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 67)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 68)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 69)
- 03-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 70)
- 03-03-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 71)
- 03-03-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 72)
- 06-02-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #6, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 73)
- 06-02-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #6 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 74)
- 05-01-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #5, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 75)
- 05-01-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #5 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 76)
- 03(04)-03-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 77)
- 03(04)-03-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 78)
- 03-03-1-2 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 79)
- 03-03-1-2 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 80)
- 03-03-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 81)
- 03-03-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 82)
- 04-02-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 83)
- 04-02-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 84)
- 04-02-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 85)
- 04-02-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 86)
- 03-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 87)
- 03-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 88)
- 03-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 89)
- 03-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 90)
- 03-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 91)
- 03-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 92)
- Alcoholism Research Program - Correspondence with Russ Tagert, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Notes on Conversation with Dr. Harley at Western Electric, Lexington Road Plant, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Notes on Interviews Conducted at North Carolina Plants, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Western Electric Individual Case Data - The Carolinas, 1973-1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #12, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #12 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #11, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #11 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- 01-14-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #10, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- 01-14-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #9 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- 14-01-2-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- 14-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 51)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 54)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #19, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 55)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #19 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 56)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 57)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 58)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 59)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 60)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #16, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 61)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #16 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 62)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #15, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 63)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #15 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 64)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 65)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 66)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #26, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 67)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #26 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 68)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #25, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 69)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #25 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 70)
- 01-14-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #24, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 71)
- 01-14-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #24 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 72)
- 01-14-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #23, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 73)
- 01-14-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #23 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 74)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #22, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 75)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #22 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 76)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #21, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 77)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #21 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 78)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #20, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 79)
- 14-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #20 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 80)
- 14-01-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 81)
- 14-01-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 82)
- 14-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 83)
- 14-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 84)
- 14-01-1-2 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 85)
- 14-01-1-2 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 86)
- 14-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 87)
- 14-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 88)
- Western Electric Individual Case Data - Los Angeles and Southern California, 1975-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- L.G. Davis - Personnel Information Summary, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #10, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #9 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- 11-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- 12-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- 11-03-3-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- 11-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 48)